Alex Thayn

Highland, UT 84003 | 801-669-3090 | alexthayn1@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/alex-thayn

SUMMARY

Upcoming B.S. Software Engineering Senior working toward a software engineering degree with an emphasis in web development. Strong Foundation in object-oriented programming and software design principles. Experienced in developing, testing, and debugging code. Focused on designing exceptional code that is maintainable and reusable.

EDUCATION

Snow College, Ephraim, UT - BS Software Engineering

Anticipated graduation: May 2019 / GPA: 3.9 / Dean's List (6 semesters)

SKILLS

- C# and XAML
- SQL / T-SQL
- Java
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
- C/C++
- Android Development
- Python
- Linux
- Design Patterns

- Experience in Agile Scrum Work Environment
- Relational Database Design
- Git and Mercurial version control
- Dedicated to Test Driven Development
- AWS Cloud Computing Certified
- Technical Communication / Writing Skills
- Continuous Learner and Problem Solver
- Solid grasp of Object Oriented Principles
- Reliable and Motivated Team Member

EXPERIENCE

Autonomous Solutions Inc, Petersboro, UT - Software Engineering Intern / May 2018 - August 2018

- Researched and implemented solutions for the process of localizing and internationalizing Mobius (ASI's Vehicle Command and Control Software)
- Assisted in finding and fixing defects found in Mobius while tracking progress in Jira
- Coded in an Agile environment utilizing a test-driven development approach
- Collaborated with technical lead and other team members to form a team effort in development
- Profiled Mobius and fixed memory leaks and other performance issues

Geneva Rock, Draper, UT - Lab Technician / July 2017 - August 2017

- Collaborated with team members to analyze plant materials and ensure all were within specification
- Carefully collected and measured accurate samples to ensure quality data was obtained
- Identified, documented, and reported any inconsistencies or issues with produced materials

Goal Zero, Riverton, UT - Quality Control Inspector / September 2015 - July 2016

- Tested and analyzed incoming product to ensure it met established quality specifications
- Demonstrated a methodical, detail-oriented, and thorough approach to all assignments while adhering to compressed timelines, completed all assignments on or ahead of schedule